heliopower.com 2010-05-05

# Privacy Policy | HelioPower

HelioPower collects customer information to enhance your user experience. This privacy policy is intended to assist you in understanding what information we gather about you when you visit this Web site, how we use that information, and the safeguards we have in place for that information.

This Privacy Statement applies only to the information collected online at HelioPower.com.

 **General Browsing Information**  
HelioPower.com gathers navigational information during each visitor's use of our Web site. In the process of gathering navigational information, non-personally identifiable information (i.e. domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address) may be collected. The navigational information tells HelioPower.com about the use of our Web site by visitors, including the areas of our site that are most visited or the time of a last visit to a page on our site. It also tells us about the technical efficiencies of our Web site and services (i.e. the time it takes a visitor to connect to our Web site or download pages). The navigational information helps us better understand a visitor's experience at HelioPower.com and improve upon that experience by recognizing and delivering more of the features, services and products our visitors prefer.

**USING PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ONLINE**

HelioPower.com uses the personal information we collect from you to fulfill requests that you have created, for verification purposes, to respond to your inquiries, and to deliver services and information about our products or Web site, including adding you to the HelioPower.com’s E-mail list.

**VISITORS FROM OUTSIDE THE U.S**

If you are visiting HelioPower.com from a location outside of the U.S., your orders placed through HelioPower.com will be accepted and fully processed in and shipped from the U.S. All information you provide will be maintained in our Web servers and/or internal systems located within the U.S., and protected as noted in this privacy policy.

**COOKIES**

What are cookies and how do we use cookies on our Web site?  
HelioPower.com uses a browser feature known as a cookie. A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your computer. Cookies are used to help track your clicks and pass information as you go through the pages within HelioPower.com. This allows HelioPower.com to make our site more responsive to your needs by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. HelioPower.com also uses cookies to keep track of how many items you put into your shopping bag and to remember you when you return to HelioPower.com.

We also use cookies and/or a technology known as clear gifs, which are typically stored in e-mails to help us confirm your receipt of, and response to, our e-mails and to provide you a more personalized experience. Cookies can allow us to associate navigational information from browsing visits with personal information you provide at our site.

**UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your personal information including billing and shipping information by logging into your account.

**PRIVACY OF CHILDREN ON OUR WEB SITE**

To ensure compliance with federal law, HelioPower.com does not knowingly collect or maintain information provided by children under the age of 13.

**QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS**

If you have questions or concerns with respect to our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us.

**SECURITY STATEMENT**

HelioPower.com takes the following types of security measures: use of technologies and policies such as limited access data-centers, firewall technology, secure socket layer certificate authentication and limitations of administrative access to our systems. In addition, it is our policy not to send your credit card number via e-mail. In fact, this is a practice we encourage you to adopt in all of your Internet activities.

We designed HelioPower.com to accept orders only from Web browsers that permit communication through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology; for example, 4.0 versions or higher of Netscape Navigator, versions 5.01 or higher of Internet Explorer, versions 0.8 or higher of Firefox and versions 1.2 or higher of Safari.

While we implement the above security measures on this site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.

This Privacy Statement is effective January 1, 2009
